# Jesse Packwood

### Software Engineer

jesse@lokithewolfdog.com

+ 1 317 361 0166

## Summary

Motivated full-stack engineer who values efficiency, diversity, and the ability to contribute to a team. E-commerce experience and a challenging Turing education combine to make a better leader and developer with regards to product innovation and user focus.

## **Projects**

#### Coin Watch

https://jessepackwood.github.io/ CoinWatch

#### React, Redux, Firebase

Cryptocurrency tracking web app pulls coincap.io api to watch specific coin performance and track a user generated portfolio.

#### Movie Tracker

https://github.com/katiescruggs/movie-tracker-frontend

#### React, Redux, Postgres

Web app utilizing the movieDB api to pull the most recently released films so a user can sign in and favorite films to their account.

### **SWapiBox**

https://github.com/jessepackwood/ swapiBox

#### React

Star Wars api is used to render data about the movies series characters, vehicles, and planets.

### **Skills**

#### Techical

JavascriptHTML5GitNode.jsReactCSS3TDDLightroomReduxSASS/SCSSSketchPhotoshop

#### **Professional**

Activator Collaboration Analytical Adaptability

### Experience

Fly Lords 2018 - Present

#### **Content Creator**

- Destination Photographer for ad campaigns with major brands in the fly fishing and outdoors industries
- Attract new clients through social media networking and industry events

#### The Loki Project

2017 - Present

#### Web Engineer and Customer Service Manager

- Designing and building web pages with image galleries and ecommerce products
- Adobe Lightroom Preset designer and customer service manger

#### **AAR Aircraft Services**

2011 - 2013

#### Material Handler

Oversaw parts inventory and delivery

### Education

#### Turing School of Software and Design 2017 - 2018

- Graduated from 1708 Front-End Cohort

### Indianapolis University of Indianapolis 2010 - 2015

- BA Economics

- Kelley School of Business